

# PE HAO CHEAH

No 8, Jalan PU 2/7, ↑
Taman Puchong Utama
016-3313-878 ↓
cheahpehao@gmail.com



### **INTRODUCTION**

I am a 22 years old Malaysian Chinese that freshly graduated from Universiti Tunku Abdul Rahman (UTAR) after finishing my degree – Bachelor of Science (Hons) Game Development with a graduating CGPA of 2.90.

I am computer literate, and a fast learner. My native language is Mandarin Chinese, but I can also speak fluent English, and communicate fairly well in Bahasa Malaysia. I can also understand Cantonese and Hokkien dialects as well.

I may be fresh, but I am very eager and willing to learn new things. I am also able to adapt to my work environment fairly quickly.



#### **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Science (Hons) Game Development @ Universiti Tunku Abdul Rahman (UTAR)

MAY 2015 - MAY 2018

I finished my studies with a final CGPA of 2.90. My top subjects are Web Application Development, Computer Graphics using OpenGL and Mobile Game Developments.

# Senior Middle Three (Science Stream) @ Chong Hwa Independent High School Kuala Lumpur (CHKL)

JANUARY 2009 - DECEMBER 2014

Graduated my six-years secondary education with 2As in UEC, and 3As in SPM with Bahasa Malaysia and Sejarah scoring B+ and B respectively.



#### **EXPERIENCE**

### IT Admin | Han Culture Centre (M) Sdn Bhd

JULY 2018 - CURRENT

I am responsible for the design and development of my company's website.

I am also responsible to provide level 1 and level 2 technical support by handling and resolving day-to-day computer hardware and software related issues that the company staffs encountered.

# Intern as Android Developer | Globaltium Sdn Bhd

JUNE 2017 – AUGUST 2017

My responsibility is to develop native Android application using Android Studio that the client asked. I have to coordinate and cooperate with the designers and the backend developers. During the internship, I have involved in the development of two Android application and exposed to the Android application development environment.

#### IT Assistant | Chong Hwa Independent High School (CHKL)

#### JANUARY 2015 - MAY 2015

My responsibility is to provide helpdesk and level 1 technical support to the teachers with computer hardware and software related issues such as troubleshooting to identify the issue with their computer, and provide a solution for them.



## **SKILLS**

#### **Language Proficiency (0 = Poor; 10 = Excellent)**

Language	Proficiency
Mandarin	9
English	8
Cantonese	7
Malay	6
Hokkien	5

## **Programming Language Proficiency (0 = Poor; 10 = Excellent)**

Language	Proficiency
HTML	8
JavaScript	8
C-sharp for Unity	5
Android Studio	3
Java	3

#### Other skills:

- Able to troubleshoot, and identify problem on a computer
- Fast learner
- Unity Engine
- Web Development using HTML CSS JS